TIHAM HOSSAIN KHAN

296,Kazi Bari Road, Uttara, Dhaka **↑** +8801783-771049 ****

Tihamhossain.th@gmail.com 💌

https:/www.linkedin.com/feed in

https://twitter.com/khan_tiham



OBJECTIVE

Honor Roll Student and active in Basketball and Music. Experienced in Constructive Coding, Team Management and creating a great Client Communication Experience. Straight A student in Mathematics, Programming, English, Electrical and Team-leader of CSE Basketball.



EDUCATION

Secondary School Certificate | School 2012 – 2014

GPA: 5.00

Higher School Certificate | School 2014 – 2016

GPA: 5.00



EXPERIENCE

Database Developer | SkyLark Soft. Limited February 2020 – April 2020

- Creating the basic structures of data management system
- Analyzing the Optimal solution for data reserve
- Implementing the Operation and build an User Friendly Environment

Construction Site Management

May 2020 – Present

• Leading a whole team of laborers on a Construction Site.

Content Creator | Market Desk USA September 2020 – Present

- YouTube content writer and Consultant.
- Looking forward to host a show on YouTube.

Web Developer | Nawabi Organic Food August 2020 - Present

• Developing and Designing Website.

ACHIEVEMENTS

- o One time Basketball Champion from Department of CSE
- o Participated the National Tournament of Bangabandhu Inter-University Championship

o One time champion of BAUET Coding Contest, and placed 5th on another one of these.

X

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES / FRAMEWORK

- C
- C++
- Assembly Language
- DOS box
- Sci-kit Learn
- Tensorflow

- Python
- html & CSS
- Java
- PHP
- LARAVEL Framework



SKILLS / COURSES / SOFTWARE / LANGUAGE

- English Fluent
- Arabic Moderate
- Data Analytics Novice

- Guitar Excellent
- Microsoft Office Proficient
- MySQL Strong



- > Looking forward to build a successful career in Research and Development area.
- Acting General Secretary of Dhaka Students Association of BAUET (DSAB).
- Acting Assistant General Secretary of BAUET Cultural Club (BCC).
- And also an Organizing Secretary of BAUET Sports Club.
- ➤ Have experience of working with Preachers and feeding the famished.